sce.com 2009-12-18

# SCE - Privacy Policy

Southern California Edison (SCE) respects the privacy of our customers. We realize that customer concerns about privacy and the secure transfer, storage, and use of personal information have increased with the growth of online services. That’s why SCE maintains strict privacy policies and uses state-of-the-art technologies to safeguard customer information.

 This page offers information on the following topics related to our privacy policies and practices:

  **What kind of information do we collect?**  
When you visit our Web site there are two kinds of information that we are likely to record:

> 1\. Non-personal statistical information collected in the aggregate. 

This is anonymous information on subjects such as: how many visitors come to our Web site, how they navigate through the site, which browsers they use to visit the site, etc. 

> 2\. Personal information that you knowingly supply to us.

When you sign up for certain products or register on the SCE Web site to access your account information, SCE will collect personal information that will help us to identify you, authenticate you, and provide you better service in the future. This information is called “personally identifiable information” and is used to associate usage information with a specific individual or entity. Examples of personally identifiable information are: customer name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, account number, etc. It is a common business practice to collect “personally identifiable information” in order to conduct business and provide customers with specific services. SCE has collected this information from customers in the past to provide services through mail or over the telephone. The emergence and popularity of the Internet provides SCE with yet another way to communicate with customers and meet customer needs. 

**We do not sell or trade customer information.  
** SCE will not sell or trade your personal information to any third party, absent authorization by you. In fact, because we are a regulated utility, the California Public Utilities Commission forbids us to do so. The Internet medium will not change this.  We only collect your personal data in order to provide you with better services.

  **Receipt of E-mails**  
E-mail gives SCE another convenient avenue to communicate with its customers. We hope to periodically tell you about new rates, products, and services that would benefit you. SCE will not, however, send you e-mails if you do not wish to receive them. If at anytime you would like to remove yourself from SCE’s e-mail list, you can do so by updating your profile information within [**My Account**.](http://www.sce.com/sma/)

  **Security**  
All transfers of personal information on SCE.com are secured by the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. SSL prohibits other Web users from gaining access to your personal information.

  **Children**  
SCE does not seek to collect personal information from children under 18 years of age.  We do not have any content on our site that would be considered harmful to children and certainly do not restrict children from visiting our site. In fact, we have a site specifically for children called the SCE Kids Electrical Safety World. This site is designed to educate children and teachers about basic electricity facts and history. It is particularly useful for providing safety information. At this site, children may send e-mail questions or comments to us. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect any specific personally identifiable information from children at this site, beyond their e-mail address; and we only collect a child’s e-mail address to respond to a one-time request from the child, after which the child’s e-mail address is deleted, or with advance verifiable parental consent.

  **Linked Web Sites**   
The SCE Web site contains links to various other Web sites. Please be aware that these other sites may have privacy policies that differ from SCE’s. SCE is in no way responsible for either the content that appears on linked sites, or your privacy once you have linked to other sites. 

**Updates**  
In order to improve our service or to keep up with future industry changes, the information in this privacy policy may be periodically updated. We will post a new date in the event that the current policy is altered. This statement posted December 2000.
